<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="appName">Kindness</string>

	<string name="locationError">Location Error</string>
	<string name="locationErrMsg">In order to report kindness, you must enable location services on your device and grant location permissions to this app.</string>
	<string name="unknownErrMsg">Unknown location services error. You will not be able to report kindness until the error is fixed.</string>

	<string name="reportKindness">Report Kindness</string>
	<string name="gifts">Gifts</string>
	<string name="service">Service</string>
	<string name="time">Time</string>
	<string name="touch">Touch</string>
	<string name="words">Words</string>

	<string name="category">category</string>
	<string name="latitude">latitude</string>
	<string name="longitude">longitude</string>
	<string name="thanks">Thank you for reporting an act of kindness.</string>
	<string name="toMap">Return to Map</string>

	<string name="howTo">How to Use</string>
	<string name="instruction1">Tap the plus icon to report kindness near you. Or simply explore details about the /acts of kindness/ of others by zooming in on the map.</string>
	<string name="instruction2">Tap the icon that best reflects the kindness you would like to report.</string>
	<string name="instruction3">Return to the map to see your new act of kindness added at your location.</string>

	<string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
	<string name="sharingLocation">Determining and Sharing Location</string>
	<string name="privacyTest">Determing your location - The Services deal with location, so in order to work, the Services need to know your location. Whenever you open and use/interact with this app on your mobile device, we use the location information from your mobile device (e.g., latitude and longitude) The information will only be used when you
	accept to enable your GPS location. Your location will then be used to pin point on the map where an act of kindness occurs. We do not use your GPS location for other reasons. Only when you add a Random act of kindness occurence. If you wish to turn off these services, you are able to turn off your GPS location by going to settings. Next open the Apps tab. Then scroll down and select Configure Apps or App Settings, then App permissions. Here you can select what inforamtion the apps have access to including you location.  </string>

	<string name="about">About</string>
	<string name="appDescr">A simple way to report acts of kindness. This app is designed, written, and maintained by students at Brigham Young University - Idaho.</string>
	<string name="eula">To the fullest extent allowed by law, this software comes with no warranty, either express or implied. By installing and/or using this software you agree to hold harmless Brigham Young University - Idaho and its sponsors, employees, and students.</string>
	<string name="feedback">Thank you for using Kindness! We appreciate your comments, questions, and recommendations to help us improve this app. You can contact us through the <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=edu.byui.cit.kindness">Google Play Store</a>.</string>
	<string name="contribs">Contributors</string>
	<string name="winter2018">Winter 2018</string>
	<string name="spring2018">Spring 2018</string>
	<string name="logoCredit">We created the logo and icons for Kindness using the free tools at <a href="https://logomakr.com">logomakr.com</a></string>

	<string name="mistake">Well, this is embarrassing. Something is wrong with this page, and it isn\'t working. We apologize.</string>
</resources>
